OK, Philip. This is your third cup of coffee.
We should get to work,
or we won't be finished by dinnertime.
I guess we must.
We must.
OK. The beginning of my famous Thanksgiving apple pie.
One apple. Two apples. Three apples. Four apples.
Come on, Philip!
Get busy with your famous apple pie.
There's much more to be done.
Now, the ingredients.
What goes into my apple pie besides apples?
Ah, yes. Flour, sugar, butter.
Butter, nice and cold and hard.
OK, here are the walnuts.
Last but not least,
the reason my apple pie is famous--cinnamon.
Cinnamon ...
Ellen, where's the cinnamon?
If there is any cinnamon,
it's in the cabinet with the salt and pepper.
Salt, pepper, dill weed, garlic powder, cinnamon. Ellen?
Yes, Philip.
Is it possible that we forgot to buy cinnamon?
Yes, it is possible that we forgot to buy cinnamon.
Well, how can I make my famous apple pie without cinnamon?
Good morning.
Oh, hi, Robbie. Good morning.
Good morning. Robbie.
Can you do me a favor?
Sure, Dad. What?
Remember my apple pie on Thanksgiving?
What do you love about it?
The apples?
No. The sssss...
Cinnamon.
Right. We don't have any cinnamon.
I'll go down to Henry's grocery. He's always open.
I'll get some for you.
That's my boy!
Oh, put your heavy jacket on, Robbie.
It's cold outside.
Alexandra might call.
Tell her I'll call her right back.
OK.
Thanks, Son.
Uh, why does he always have to slam the door?
Hello.... Hello, Alexandra. How are you? ... Fine.
Robbie just went to the store.
He'll be back soon.
He said he'll call you.
... Oh, oh, I see.... Oh ... certainly. ...
Well, do you have the phone number there?
... Oh ... I see.... Please, I know he wants to talk to you.... ...
Thank you,
and happy Thanksgiving to you and your family, too.
Try to come by later for dessert.... Bye.
That was Alexandra.
She and the Molinas
are going to spend Thanksgiving with their cousins.
She doesn't have the phone number.
Oh, Robbie will be disappointed.
He'll be grouchy.
Maybe she'll call back. She promised.
Here's your cinnamon, Pop.
It was a dollar and sixty cents.
You forgot to ask me for the change.
Or did you forget to give it to me?
Thanks, Son.
Alexandra called.
I'll call her back.
She said she'll call you later.
She's not at home.
You should have your breakfast, Son.
Make you feel better.
Protein, vitamins.
She said she'll call back?
Yes, she did.
Good morning, everyone!
Happy Turkey Day!
What's wrong?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
What's gotten into him?
He missed a phone call.
From ...?
Yes, Alexandra.
It's nice to see young love.... Oh, to be young again!
Where's the coffee?